export default {
  title: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
  syllables: [
    {
      question: '절',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅈ'
    }, {
      question: '쩔',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅉ'
    }, {
      question: '철',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅊ'
    }, {
      question: '짐',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅈ'
    }, {
      question: '찜',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅉ'
    }, {
      question: '침',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅊ'
    }, {
      question: '자',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅈ'
    }, {
      question: '짜',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅉ'
    }, {
      question: '차',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅊ'
    }, {
      question: '죽',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅈ'
    }, {
      question: '쭉',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅉ'
    }, {
      question: '축',
options: "ㅈ ㅉ ㅊ",
      answer: 'ㅊ'
    }
  ]
}
